

## Randyl P. Boadilla

### **CONTACT ME**

- **L** 09275388373/09760674980
- boadilla.randyl@gmail.com
- Empire Hilltop, Payatas B, Quezon City

#### **EDUCATION**

# St. Dominic Institute - Fairview (2015-2019)

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology, *Dean's Lister* 

Justice Cecilia Munoz Palma High School (2010-2014)

### **SKILLS**

- Proficient in troubleshooting and resolving technical issues.
- Strong knowledge of computer hardware, software, and operating systems.
- Excellent customer service and interpersonal skills.
- Ability to communicate technical information to non-technical users effectively.
- Experience with remote desktop support tools and techniques.
- Experience in diagnosing and resolving hardware and softwarerelated problems.

#### **PROFILE**

A dedicated and highly skilled Computer Technician with 4 years of experience in diagnosing, repairing, and maintaining a wide range of computer hardware and software systems. Experienced at providing technical support to end-users, troubleshooting complex issues, and ensuring optimal system performance.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Sales Associate/Computer Technician October 2019 - Present GJAX Computer Trading

- Answering customer inquiries and resolving product issues.
- Arranging product displays to attract customer attention.
- Keeping track of product inventory and restocking shelves as needed.
- Identifying opportunities to upsell additional products or services.
- Demonstrating expertise in photo editing for product posting and advertisement in Social Media.
- Consistently working to meet or exceed assigned sales targets and quotas.
- Performing basic computer hardware repairs, such as replacing components (e.g., RAM, Storage, GPU, etc..).
- Arranging for more complex repairs through authorized service providers.
- Assisting customers with software-related problems, including operating system issues and software installations.
- Providing guidance on updating or upgrading software.

# OJT Trainee, Technical Support July 2018 - October 2018 DENR, Central Office

- Basic troubleshooting of Computer Hardware
- Assisting end-users with network-related issues, including connectivity problems, VPN setup, and Wi-Fi access.
- Providing guidance on connecting devices to the network.
- Diagnosing and resolving network connectivity issues, including hardware and software problems.
- Investigating and fixing network outages or disruptions.

Professional references available upon request.